By 2004, the Internet had become a part of everyday life.
It was a place for connecting, learning, sharing and collaborating.
But something wasn’t right.
Web users wanted to explore without being spied on, preyed on, or ripped off,
but viruses, spyware, popups and adware were everywhere.
The only thing personalized about the experience was the information being gathered about users without their knowledge.
It was time to take back the web so it could serve its original purpose:
…enriching the lives of individuals.
From this simple, powerful desire… came Firefox,
specifically built to make the web better,
born of an open system
where the design of the software could be shared, customized and improved upon…
by anyone, anywhere, anytime.
As word and code spread, Firefox inspired a community
that sees the web as a living thing that must be nurtured to grow and thrive.
People worldwide are embracing this ecology of ideas and supporting a system that’s all about their needs and interests
and keeping the internet a vibrant, exciting place. Designed by everyone, it’s for everyone.
Over one billion downloads later
it shows no signs of slowing down.
With Firefox, life online can reflect who users really are.
From how they see it
connect with it
share it
to how they grow with it.
Firefox is here to help them find their own way
moving at the speed of their imagination.
We’ve come so far in just five years
imagine what we can do together in the next five.
Let’s keep the Internet healthy, open
and the creative fires burning bright.
Light the world with Firefox.